Gregg Smith Singers Recordings
Gregg Smith Singers Recordings
- Recordings
  - GSS (2), 3/9/1993; gss_456; Recording of piano, men's chorus, antiphonal men's chorus, women's choir and soprano solos with comments.; 1/2 inch audio tape (Oversize 36)
    201-206: (piano, men's chorus, antiphonal men's chorus); 207-211: (piano, men's chorus, antiphonal men's chorus, women's choir, soprano solo)
  - GSS (3), 3/9/1993; gss_457; Recording of piano, mixed choirs, men's choir - antiphonal, soprano performances.; 1/2 inch audio tape (Oversize 36)
    Cont'd from 456: 301-311: (piano, mixed choirs, soprano); 312-313: (piano, men's choir - antiphonal)
  - GSS (4), 03/09/1993; gss_017; 1/2 inch audio tape (Oversize 2)
  - GSS (5), 3/9/1993; gss_458; Recording of piano, women's and men's choirs and soprano performances.; 1/2 inch audio tape (Oversize 36)
    Cont'd from 457: 501-506/507/509/512: (piano, women's choirs); 507-508/513: (piano, women's and men's choirs, soprano)
  - GSS (6), 3/9/1993; gss_459; Recording of piano, women's and men's choirs and soprano performances.; 1/2 inch audio tape (Oversize 36)
    Cont'd from 458: 601-610: (piano, women's choir, men's choir, soprano)
  - GSS (7), 3/9/1993; gss_460; Recording of women's and men's choirs performances with conversations at the end.; 1/2 inch audio tape (Oversize 36)
    Cont'd from 459: 701-707: (women's choir, men's choir); 708: "I am a poet"; "Merry-Go-Round" (women's choir, men's choir)
  - GSS (1), 02/28/1994; gss_441; Recording of piano, chours, alto solo with comments.; 1/2 inch audio tape (Oversize 33)
    101-110: "On the table clock" (piano, chorus, alto solo, clapping); 102: "Karen" (piano, chorus, alto solo, clapping)
  - GSS (2), 2/28/1994; gss_442; Recording of chorus, piano, soprano with comments.; 1/2 inch audio tape (Oversize 35)
    All segments oft the same work: 210: (chorus, piano); 112-115/122-123: "Put him onto the case..."(chorus, piano); 115-119: "Put him onto the case..."(chorus, piano, soprano); 120: (piano)
  - GSS (3), 2/28/1994; gss_443; Recording of mixed chorus, acapella performance with comments.; 1/2 inch audio tape (Oversize 35)
    Cont'd from 442:123/125: (chorus, piano); 126-128/130: "Sustainance"; "Two alike" (chorus, acapella); 129: "Kiss" (chorus, acapella); 131-133: "Dust" (chorus, acapella)
  - GSS (4), 02/28/1994; gss_015; 134 - 201 incomplete; 1/2 inch audio tape (Oversize 2)
  - GSS (5), 2/28/1994; gss_444; Recording of mixed chorus, acapella performance with comments.; 1/2 inch audio tape (Oversize 35)
    201-211: (mixed chorus, acapella)
  - GSS (6), 2/28/1994; gss_445; Recording of mixed chorus, acapella performance with comments.; 1/2 inch audio tape (Oversize 35)
    211-220: "Drinking of the wind that is to come" (mixed chorus, acapella)
  - GSS (7), 2/28/1994; gss_446; Recording of mixed chorus, acapella performance with comments.; 1/2 inch audio tape (Oversize 35)
    Cont'd from 445: 220-228: (mixed chorus, acapella)
  - GSS (8), 2/28/1994; gss_447; Recording of mixed chorus, acapella performance.; 1/2 inch audio tape (Oversize 35)
    228-229: "Persimmons fall" (mixed chorus, acapella, piano fragment at end)
  - GSS (1), 02/16/1995; gss_005; Mixed choir and soloist with organ; 1/2 inch audio tape (Oversize 1)
  - GSS (2), 02/16/1995; gss_006; Mixed choir and soloist with organ; 1/2 inch audio tape (Oversize 1)
  - GSS (3), 02/16/1995; gss_007; Mixed choir with organ; 1/2 inch audio tape (Oversize 1)
  - GSS (4), 02/16/1995; gss_008; Mixed choir with organ; 1/2 inch audio tape (Oversize 1)
  - GSS (5), 02/16/1995; gss_009; Mixed choir with organ; 1/2 inch audio tape (Oversize 1)
  - GSS (6), 02/16/1995; gss_010; Mixed choir and soloist with organ; 1/2 inch audio tape (Oversize 1)
  - GSS (7), 02/16/1995; gss_011; Pipe organ; 1/2 inch audio tape (Oversize 2)
  - GSS (1), 05/08/1995; gss_022; Soprano, choir, piano and acapella; 1/2 inch audio tape (Oversize 3)
  - GSS (2), 05/08/1995; gss_023; Soprano, choir, acapella; 1/2 inch audio tape (Oversize 3)
  - GSS (3), 05/08/1995; gss_024; 1/2 inch audio tape (Oversize 3)
  - GSS (4), 05/08/1995; gss_025; 1/2 inch audio tape (Oversize 3)
  - GSS (5), 05/08/1995; gss_026; Additional note by the audio engineer RJH reads: "recorded in church".; 1/2 inch audio tape (Oversize 3)
  - GSS (6), 05/08/1995; gss_027; Note by the audio engineer RJH reads: "Roz solos, chorus. Airplanes interfere"; 1/2 inch audio tape (Oversize 3)
  - GSS (106A ) Rorem - Paris, gss_544; 1/2 inch audio tape (Oversize 44)
  - GSS (107A ) Riley; [Alf] Houkum; [Ann] Silsbee, gss_545; 1/2 inch audio tape (Oversize 44)
    Running times: 1: Houkum (6:17); 2: Cantata 2 (9:55); Riley: Magnum (17:06); Silsbee (22:35)
  - GSS (112A ) [Louise] Talma, gss_546; 1/2 inch audio tape (Oversize 44)
  - GSS (112B), gss_547; 1/2 inch audio tape (Oversize 44)
    Talma ships: 1 Larseu; 2 Calloway; 3 Talma sonnets
  - GSS (102B), gss_669; 1/4 inch audio tape (Oversize 52)
  - GSS (102B-3), gss_670; Note on the box reads: "War Lament, H. B.". Inserted note in the box reads: "This tape is 30ips edited original of "A Transient view", Led Smit".; 1/4 inch audio tape (Oversize 52)
  - GSS (106A), gss_671; 1/4 inch audio tape; running time 25:54 (Oversize 52)
  - GSS (106B), gss_672; 1/4 inch audio tape; running time 27:43 (Oversize 52)
  - GSS (106B last), gss_673; 1/2 inch audio tape (Oversize 52)
  - GSS (107A), gss_674; 1/4 inch audio tape; running time 22:35 (Oversize 52)
  - GSS (107B), gss_675; 1/4 inch audio tape; running time 21:46 (Oversize 52)
  - GSS (111B), gss_937; 1/2 inch audio tape (SCRC 19:D:1)
    [Ross Lee] Finney (7); [James] Furman (4); [Robert] Stern
  - GSS (111A), gss_938; 1/2 inch audio tape (SCRC 19:D:1)
    [Brian] Fennelly (2); [Darrell] Handel; [Mel] Powell (6); [Bain] Murray
  - GSS - "Sweethearts", gss_939; 1/4 inch audio tape (SCRC 19:D:1)
  - GSS - "Sweethearts", gss_940; 1/4 inch audio tape (SCRC 19:D:1)
  - GSS - Bee[?], gss_944; Jack Beeson?; 1/2 inch audio tape (Oversize 61)
  - GSS - Josquin [Des Prez]: Dies Irae, gss_461; Recording of Josquin's: Dies Irae for small orchestra, oboe or bassoon, trumpet or cornet, bass, tenor, choir.; 1/2 inch audio tape (Oversize 36)
    oboe or bassoon, trumpet or cornet, small orchestra, bass, tenor, choir
  - GSS [Dan] Locklair, gss_180; Additional notes by the audio engineer read: "1: ? (piano, basses, altos, tenors, hand bells, mixed choir, whistling (?), sopranos (very atmospheric)"; 1/2 inch audio tape (Oversize 14)
  - GSS [Jack] Gottlieb: Presidential Suite, gss_189; 1/2 inch audio tape (Oversize 15)
    1: "Ask Not What Your Country...." (mixed choir, unaccomp.); 2: "Doo Dah ...You Can Fool Some of the People" (mixed choir, unaccomp.); 3: "President Cooledge..." (mixed choir, unaccomp.); 4: "The Buck Stops Here" (mixed choir, unaccomp., whistling); 5: "Thomas Jefferson..." (mixed choir, unaccomp.. alto solo); 6: "Oya, Oya. Boom chic a, Boom chic a" (chorus, sound effects); 7: "This Generation of Americans Has a Rendezvous..." (choir)
  - GSS [Kurt] Weill, gss_169; 1/2 inch audio tape (Oversize 13)
    1: "Yes, where ever the hills have broken down..." (orchestra, tenor solos, chorus, spoken word, baritone solo); 2: "lord of the height, look down on our early pilgrimage" (orchestra, solos, chorus); 3: "Cry the beloved country" (oboe solo, orchestra, tenor, solo, chorus, soprano solo, orchestra)
  - GSS [Kurt] Weill/ Ross /Sowash, gss_170; 1/2 inch audio tape (Oversize 13)
    1: "O Billyo" (chorus, tenor, soprano solos, baritone); 2: "A[?] on the tablecloth" (chorus, piano accompaniment, soprano solo); 3: "Diogenes..." (the philosopher) (chorus, tenor, sopranos, baritones, unaccomp.); 4: "Diogenes..." (not the same as 3) (chorus, unaccomp.); 5: "Diogenes..." (not the same as 3 or 4) (chorus, baritones, sopranos, tenors)
  - GSS [Ned] Rorem GNDLA, gss_164; Sheet music for ":Four Madrigals" by Ned Rorem is inserted in the box.; 1/4 inch audio tape (Oversize 13)
  - GSS [Stephen] Sondheim, gss_167; 1/2 inch audio tape (Oversize 13)
    1: "I remember sky" (soprano solo, chorus, piano accompaniment)
  - GSS [William] Schman Rounds, gss_159; 1/2 inch audio tape (Oversize 12)
    "Early to Bed, Early to Rice" (chorus, unaccompanied); "He that Goes a Borrowing"; (money); "Look Before you Leap"; "All that Glitter's Is Not Gold"; "Make Haste, Make Waster"
  - GSS [William] Schuman Orpheus/[Whitman] Carols, gss_158; 1/2 inch audio tape (Oversize 12)
    No slate: "Orpheus" (piano accompanying Ros. solo); 3 Carols of Death (choir)
  - GSS at Holly 3 (5); [James] Furman; [William] Schuman (1), 04/11/1953; gss_883; 1/4 inch audio tape (Oversize 59)
  - GSS at Holly III (1), 11/21/1983; gss_887; 1/4 inch audio tape (Oversize 59)
  - GSS B Capella Byrd Schmigital (2), gss_927; 1/2 inch audio tape (SCRC 19:D:1)
  - GSS Billingsharon; Schubert; [Guillaume] Dufay; Magnum, gss_179; Additional note on the box reads: "Sharon 3:10; Schubert 4:11; Dufay 1:36; O Magnum 7:40; Reduce level 4db for Schubert onward".; 1/2 inch audio tape (Oversize 14)
    1: "I am the Rose of Sharon..." (mixed chorus, sung in madrigal form, unacomp.); 2: In German - from Schubert song cycle (piano accompaniment, baritone solo, songs in German, mixed chorus, sopranos, tenor solo; 3: "Gloria Deo...", DuFay (mixed chorus, unaccomp.); 4: "O Magnum" (piano accomp., soprano solo, mixed chorus)
  - GSS Britten: Choral Dances, gss_162; Additional notes by the audio engineer RJH read: "Unaccompanied chorus".; 1/2 inch audio tape (Oversize 12)
    1. Time; 2. Concord; 3. Time and Concord; 4. Country Girls; 5. Rustics and Fishermen; 6. Final Dance of Homage
  - GSS Brubeck, gss_559; Note on the box reads: "reduce level 3-4db peaks about 2 min. from end".; 1/2 inch audio tape; running time 28:05 (Oversize 45)
  - GSS Brubeck, gss_560; 1/2 inch audio tape (Oversize 45)
  - GSS Busby, gss_558; 1/2 inch audio tape (Oversize 45)
  - GSS Carter (1), gss_692; 1/4 inch audio tape (Oversize 53)
  - GSS Chaudoir, gss_190; Additional notes by the audio engineer RJH read: "1: Piece about Cats (chorus, unaccomp.); A-D ?".; 1/2 inch audio tape (Oversize 15)
  - GSS Cohen [sic] 5 Psalms (master), gss_191; Additional note by the audio engineer reads: "Is Cohn right spelling?".; 1/2 inch audio tape (Oversize 15)
    1: "... have I Cried Unto Thee?" (saxophone, drums, bass, chorus, flute, alto solo); 2: "Praise The Name Of the Lord..." (saxophone, drums, bass, chorus, flute, alto solo, with clapping); 3: "My Lord is My Shepherd" (23 Psalm) (saxophone, drums, bass, chorus, flute, soprano solo with clapping); 4: "Bless the Lord, O, My Soul" (103 Psalm) (baritone, soprano with clapping); 5: ? (chorus, soprano solo, baritone, soprano, baritone duet, clapping)
  - GSS Copland/Thomson (1), gss_036; Possibly includes Aaron Copland: Four Motets and/or Aaron Copland: In the Beginning; 1/2 inch audio tape (Oversize 4)
  - GSS Copland/Thomson (2), gss_037; Possibly includes Aaron Copland: Four Motets and/or Aaron Copland: In the Beginning; 1/2 inch audio tape (Oversize 4)
  - GSS E. London, gss_556; Note on the box reads: "Scamp? Reduce level, 2 or 3 db ref. tones"; 1/2 inch audio tape; running time 29:50 (Oversize 45)
  - GSS Echos [Louise] Talma, gss_160; 1/2 inch audio tape (Oversize 12)
  - GSS Folk (1), gss_926; 1/2 inch audio tape (SCRC 19:D:1)
  - GSS Fred Tillis (master), gss_188; 1/2 inch audio tape; running time 8:05 (Oversize 15)
    1: "Freedom" (chorus, unaccomp., percussion, whispering)
  - GSS Garcia, gss_256; 1/2 inch audio tape (Oversize 20)
    Soprano, mixed chorus, phrases in Spanish, whispered at end
  - GSS HKM (1), gss_293; 1/2 inch audio tape (Oversize 23)
    Slates: 101-106: (mixed chorus)
  - GSS HKM (2), gss_294; 1/2 inch audio tape (Oversize 24)
    Slates: 201-202: "O" (mixed chorus, unaccompt.); 203: ? (mixed chorus, unaccompt.); 204-205: "Orient" (mixed chorus, unaccompt.); 206-212: (mixed chorus, unaccompt.)
  - GSS HKM (3), gss_295; 1/2 inch audio tape (Oversize 24)
    Slates: 401-403; 301-316: ? (unaccomp. choir)
  - GSS Josquin (1), gss_553; 1/2 inch audio tape (Oversize 44)
  - GSS Josquin (2), gss_554; 1/2 inch audio tape (Oversize 44)
  - GSS Josquin (3), gss_555; 1/2 inch audio tape (Oversize 44)
  - GSS Kohn, gss_192; Additional note by the audio engineer reads: "Spelling: Kohn or Cohn?". Latin (piano, chorus); 1/2 inch audio tape (Oversize 15)
  - GSS Larsen: Doo-Wah, gss_181; 1/2 inch audio tape (Oversize 14)
    1: "Doo-Wah" (piano, mixed chorus, "Clair De lune", Debussy, incorporate)
  - GSS Menotti; Twain, gss_548; 1/2 inch audio tape (Oversize 44)
  - GSS Nolby (102A), gss_668; Note on the box reads: "The Descent (1969), Fred Fox, California State, Hayward, University singer. Harry Carter, director, Gregg Smith conductor, Marcia Murray, piano, Jerome Neff, percussion, Jack Van Geem, percussion, Steve Payson, percussion. 15 ips NAB, 2 tracks stereo. Richard Beggs Eng. Edit. AXIS 916 Keavny St. SF Cx. 94133".; 1/4 inch audio tape; running time 21:23 (Oversize 52)
  - GSS Pops, gss_163; 1/2 inch audio tape (Oversize 13)
    1: 107 straight (unaccompanied choir); 2: 106 straight (unaccompanied choir); 3: 203 cool (203A not used) (unaccompanied choir with vocal percussion); 4: 105 cool (unaccompanied choir); 5: 303 Eileen breath 4 notes before basses; 305 Eileen breath to end. "Say it with music" (Berlin) (unaccompanied choir, mixed); 6: 103 "Autumn leaves" sung in French and English choir, mixed; 7: 204. Two invoices 1 1/2; 3/12
  - GSS Samples (1), 1985; gss_165; 1/4 inch audio tape (Oversize 13)
  - GSS Samples (2), gss_166; 1/4 inch audio cassette (Oversize 13)
  - GSS Saranac (1), 1986; gss_193; 1/2 inch audio tape (Oversize 19)
    Slates: 101-124: Children's Choir (Latin or Italian?), unaccomp.
  - GSS Saranac (2), 1986; gss_194; 1/2 inch audio tape (Oversize 19)
    Slates: 201-211: Children's Choir as per gss_193; 212-216: "Lord make me an Instrument" (Adult choir, orchestra); 216: Children Choir come in, orchestra, adult choir
  - GSS Saranac (3), 1986; gss_195; 1/2 inch audio tape (Oversize 19)
    Slates: 301-317: Children's chorus, adult chorus, orchestra, "Off all that is the..."
  - GSS Saranac (4), 1986; gss_196; 1/2 inch audio tape (Oversize 19)
    Slates: (Cont'd from195) 401-416: adult chorus, orchestra
  - GSS Saranac (5), 1986; gss_197; 1/2 inch audio tape (Oversize 19)
    Slates: 501-513: Orchestra, Adult chorus
  - GSS Saranac (6), 1986; gss_198; 1/2 inch audio tape (Oversize 19)
    Slates: 601-602: Orchestra, Adult chorus; 603-604: "Amen, amen..." (Orchestra, Adult chorus); 605-608: Children's chorus (Italian or Latin); 609-618: Orchestra, baritones, sopranos, chorus
  - GSS Saranac (7), 1986; gss_199; 1/2 inch audio tape (Oversize 19)
    Slates: 701-708: Mixed chorus, orchestra; 709: Male chorus; 710: mixed chorus; 711-713: mixed chorus
  - GSS Saranac (8), 1986; gss_200; 1/2 inch audio tape (Oversize 19)
    Slates: 801-802: mixed chorus, orchestra, piano, clarinet
  - GSS Saranac (9), 1986; gss_201; 1/2 inch audio tape (Oversize 19)
    Slates: 901; 904-909: "I am the Rose of Sharon and Lily of the valley" orchestra, mixed chorus; 902-903: "I am the Rose of Sharon and Lily of the valley" orchestra
  - GSS Saranac (10), 1986; gss_202; 1/2 inch audio tape (Oversize 19)
    Slates: 1001-1012: "Rose of Sharon" (mixed chorus,orchestra)
  - GSS Saranac (11), 1986; gss_203; 1/2 inch audio tape (Oversize 19)
    Slates: 1101-1114: Orchestra, mixed chorus; 1112: "Best piece ever composed..." "Goddess of dischord"
  - GSS Saranac (12), 1986; gss_204; 1/2 inch audio tape (Oversize 19)
    Slates: 1201-1209: "When Jesus wept..." (soprano solo, Roz.); 1210: "When Jesus wept..." (soprano solo, Roz., harp, orchestra, mixed chorus); 1211-1212: "When Jesus wept...", "Lily" (soprano solo, Roz, baritone, tenor solos)
  - GSS Saranac (13), 1986; gss_149; Additional notes by the audio engineer RJH read: "Gentlemen with orchestra and baritone, speaking".; 1/2 inch audio tape (Oversize 11)
  - GSS Saranac (14), 1986; gss_150; Additional notes by the audio engineer RJH read: "Choir and orchestra, Yankee doodle, orchestra; mothers - children".; 1/2 inch audio tape (Oversize 11)
  - GSS Saranac (15), 1986; gss_151; 1/2 inch audio tape (Oversize 11)
    1501: "There is a Longing for" (orchestra, tenor, choir, spoken and sung monologue; 1502: "From the top", "There is a..."; 1503: "Yes, where ever" (pickup); 1504-1506: "Look down upon our earthly pilgrimage" (tenor, orchestra, choir)
  - GSS Saranac (16), 1986; gss_152; 1603: no cassette; 1/2 inch audio tape (Oversize 11)
    1601: "Wasted childhood..." (tenor, orchestra, choir) - "Cry the Beloved Country"; 1602: " I before D"
  - GSS Saranac (17), 1986; gss_153; Tones in middle; 1/2 inch audio tape (Oversize 11)
  - GSS Saranac (18), 1986; gss_154; 1/2 inch audio tape (Oversize 11)
    1601: "There is a Garden" (Ros. soprano, clarinet, harp, viola)
  - GSS Saranac (19), 1986; gss_155; 1/2 inch audio tape (Oversize 11)
    1901-2001: "Follow, happy shadow" (soprano, clarinet, harp, viola)
  - GSS Silver, gss_168; Additional notes on the box read: "Increase level Ave and Salve; Decrease level Jupitor (loud at end); Raise level 5 db!"; 1/2 inch audio tape (Oversize 13)
    1: unaccompanied chorus, "Wha hae, wha hae, Goo...", tenor
  - GSS Swickard, gss_268; 1/2 inch audio tape (Oversize 21)
    (mixed chorus, spoken lyrics and whispered lyrics): "... look no to me..."; "... upon the hillside..."; "... on hope and memory..."
  - GSS SWK and Watson (10), gss_292; 1/2 inch audio tape (Oversize 23)
    Slates: 1001-1002, 1004, 1007: (mixed chorus)
  - GSS Tarantella (1), gss_712; 1/4 inch audio tape (Oversize 54)
  - GSS Tarantella Etc. (2), gss_713; 1/4 inch audio tape (Oversize 54)
  - GSS Watson (2), gss_291; 1/2 inch audio tape (Oversize 23)
    1: "What's in a name we ask you", Watson Canon (chorus, unaccomp.); 2-3: ? Watson Canon (chorus, unaccomp.); 4: Roz speaks @ close to chorus; 5: chit-chat between everyone
  - GSS Watson Canon, gss_176; 1/2 inch audio tape (Oversize 14)
    1: What's in a Name We Ask You? (chorus, unaccomp.) "Watson Canon"
  - GSS Will [William] Schuman: Mighty Casey, gss_182; Additional notes by the audio engineer read: ""Baseball Cantata [?] (soloist, chorus, orchestra)". Note on the box reads: "VS 6143, Dolby A".; 1/4 inch audio tape; running time 32:26 (Oversize 14)
  - GSS Xmas [Christmas] (1), 1987; gss_551; 1/2 inch audio tape (Oversize 44)
  - GSS Xmas [Christmas] (2), 1987; gss_552; 1/2 inch audio tape (Oversize 44)
  - GSS, [Lukas] Foss, inc., gss_028; 1/2 inch audio tape (Oversize 3)
  - GSS: "Sound Canticle" (2), 05/10/1982; gss_898; 1/4 inch audio tape (Oversize 61)
  - Handel at Holly III (1), gss_843; 1/4 inch audio tape (Oversize 58)
  - Handel at Holly III (2), gss_844; 1/4 inch audio tape (Oversize 58)
  - Harpies (1), gss_902; Based on the GSS discography on their website, this is most likely "The Harpies" by Marc Blitzstein.; 1/4 inch audio tape (Oversize 61)
  - Harpies (2), gss_903; Based on the GSS discography on their website, this is most likely "The Harpies" by Marc Blitzstein.; 1/4 inch audio tape (Oversize 61)
  - Harpies (3), gss_907; Based on the GSS discography on their website, this is most likely "The Harpies" by Marc Blitzstein; 1/4 inch audio tape (Oversize 61)
  - [Lou] Harrison: "Mass", 04/28/1976; gss_914; 1/4 inch audio tape (Oversize 61)
  - Hawlroz (1), gss_632; 1/2 inch audio tape (Oversize 50)
  - Hawlroz (2), gss_633; 1/2 inch audio tape (Oversize 50)
  - Hawlroz (3), gss_634; 1/2 inch audio tape (Oversize 50)
  - Hawlroz (4), gss_635; 1/2 inch audio tape (Oversize 50)
  - Hawlroz (5), gss_636; 1/2 inch audio tape (Oversize 50)
  - Hawlroz (6), gss_637; 1/2 inch audio tape (Oversize 50)
  - [Heinrich] Schütz (Tape Dub side 2), gss_772; 1/4 inch audio tape (Oversize 57)
  - [Heinrich] Schütz (Tape Dub side 2), gss_773; 1/4 inch audio tape (Oversize 57)
  - [Heinrich] Schütz: German Madrigals (Side 6), gss_782; 1/4 inch audio tape (Oversize 57)
  - [Heinrich] Schütz: Madrigals, Gregg Smith, gss_779; Label on the reel reads: "DUB down - Schütz, Reel 5: Italian Madrigals".; 1/4 inch audio tape (Oversize 57)
  - [Heinrich] Schütz: Sacred Concerti (Side I), gss_780; Label on the reel reads: "DUBBED reel - Schütz, Side I".; 1/4 inch audio tape (Oversize 57)
    Habe Deine; Die seele Christe; Veni Spiritu; Es Ging
  - [Heinrich] Schütz: Sacred Concerti (Side II), gss_781; Label on the reel reads: "Master DUB - Schütz, Side II".; 1/4 inch audio tape (Oversize 57)
    Allein Gott; O Hilf Christe; Rorate Coeli; Psalm 121
  - Hennagin: By the roadside, Nov 1982; gss_106; Hennagin: By the roadside, November, 1982 Session. Note on the back of the old box reads: PO 651, Saranac Lake, 12983.; 1/4 inch audio tape (Oversize 48)
  - Hennegreg (1), gss_131; Additional notes by the audio engineer read: "Mixed chorus. 106: Before my God".; 1/2 inch audio tape (Oversize 10)
  - Hennegreg (2), gss_132; Additional notes by the audio engineer read: "Mixed chorus. 201: Before my God".; 1/2 inch audio tape (Oversize 10)
  - Hennegreg (3), gss_133; Additional notes by the audio engineer read: "Mixed chorus".; 1/2 inch audio tape (Oversize 10)
  - Hennegreg (4), gss_134; Additional notes by the audio engineer read: "Mixed chorus".; 1/2 inch audio tape (Oversize 10)
  - Hennegreg (5), gss_135; Additional notes by the audio engineer read: "Time and Space" (mixed chorus)".; 1/2 inch audio tape (Oversize 10)
  - Hennegreg (6), gss_136; Additional notes by the audio engineer read: "Time and Space" (mixed chorus); 602: "New come to thee".; 1/2 inch audio tape (Oversize 10)
  - Hennegreg (7), gss_137; Additional notes by the audio engineer read: "Have never come to thee" (mixed chorus)".; 1/2 inch audio tape (Oversize 10)
  - Hennegreg (8), gss_138; Additional notes by the audio engineer read: "mixed chorus with soprano".; 1/2 inch audio tape (Oversize 10)
  - Hennegreg, [Michael] Hennagin (2), gss_891; 1/4 inch audio tape (Oversize 59)
  - [Paul] Hindemith: "La Belle dame Sans Merci" (The Beautiful Lady who never said Thank you), gss_896; Note on the box reads: "On 1230, this tape ran out; however we have 30 ips)".; 1/4 inch audio tape (Oversize 59)
  - [Andrew] Imbrie: On The Beach At Night, gss_183; 1/4 inch audio tape; running time 13:18 (Oversize 14)
  - [Charles] Ives - Hunter Concert, 10/18/1974; gss_771; 1/4 inch audio tape (Oversize 57)
  - [Charles] Ives/[George] Gershwin, gss_270; 1/4 inch audio tape (Oversize 21)
    1 - "Sins of Spring", Gershwin; 2 - "The Jolly Tar and the Milkmaid" from "A Damsel in Distress" Gershwin; 3 - Song, Charles Ives (chorus, soprano, piano)
  - Jazz Mass for St. Peters (edited), 1973; gss_766; 1/4 inch audio tape (Oversize 56)
    Jazz Mazz
  - Jazzmazz Tones, gss_171; 1 inch audio tape (Oversize 13)
  - Jazzmazzter (1), gss_172; 1 inch audio tape (Oversize 13)
  - Jazzmazzter (2) and Dedication, gss_173; Note on the box reads: "Fix splice in credo 1st section (Son of God). More space before Agnus Dei (1st piece after Sanctus)".; 1 inch audio tape (Oversize 14)
  - KC (4); Casey, gss_836; 1/4 inch audio tape (Oversize 58)
  - KC: "Casey" (1), gss_901; 1/4 inch audio tape (Oversize 61)
  - KC: "Casey" (2), 1976; gss_908; 1/4 inch audio tape (Oversize 61)
  - KC: "Casey" (3), gss_894; 1/4 inch audio tape (Oversize 59)
  - Lake Placid Glee Club 1981, gss_754; Note on the box reads: "Chamber: Kim, Roz, GS, Monteverdi, Waxman".; 1/4 inch audio tape (Oversize 56)
    1: Monteverdi: "Two Madrigals", Rosalind Rees, Kimbal Wheeler, Paul Suits; 2: Gregg Smith: "Omaggio a Montevverdi", Rees, Wheeler, Suits, Kosmala; 3: Don Waxman: "Four love songs"
  - Landscapes, Collect (basset), Sound Canticles, Evil, gss_622; 1/4 inch audio tape (Oversize 50)
  - Last takes [William] Schuman, gss_834; 1/4 inch audio tape (Oversize 58)